Original PDF total pages: 5

================ PAGE 1 ================
Block 1 (x=18.0, y=8.3 to 19.4): ''
Block 3 (x=39.4, y=83.3 to 176.9): 'PRIVATE AND CONFIDENTIAL \n 20 January 2025 \n \nMR. Voona Sowmith, \n+91 7095207926'
Block 4 (x=18.0, y=177.2 to 491.8): 'Sub: Employment Offer \n \nDear Voona Sowmith, \n \nSubsequent to the discussions that you had with request to your internal movement within the organization, we are pleased \nto extend an offer of employment to you from SOFTSTANDARD SOLUTIONS LLP as a US HR & Immigration \nSpecialist position. This letter sets out the key terms of the employment. Your responsibilities and duties are detailed in the \nemployment contract. \n \nYour joining date is 02 January, 2025. Please make yourself available at 7:00 PM IST in our office on that day. Your \nCTC (the cost to the company per annum is INR 3,50,000 (Three Lakhs Fifty Thousand Indian Rupees) take home \nplus incentive as variable pay. Details are available in the annexure of the employment contract. Your formal appointment \nletter will be given on the date of your joining. You will be required to sign a Non-Disclosure Agreement on joining the \norganization. \n \nSalary Reviews: The candidate must complete a minimum of one year from the date of joining to be eligible for salary \nreview. Salary review is strictly done based on individual and company performance only. Your performance will be \nassessed based on attendance, communication, deliverables, motivation, and teamwork. \n \nGeneral working hours for this position are from 7:30 PM to 4:30 AM IST, Monday to Friday. The office is closed on \nSaturday& Sunday. However, the candidate should be available on weekends at the companyÆs request. You may be \neligible for receiving compensatory off for those extra hours spent. You would also be required to be flexible to work in \nthe core EST shift on a need basis. \n \n        Reporting Head: During your working hours in office, you would be directly reporting to Kodaskar Mysa (US Accounts'
Block 5 (x=18.0, y=492.1 to 516.5): 'Manager)'
Block 6 (x=36.0, y=516.9 to 790.2): 'Probation: You will be on probation period for three months (3) from the date of your joining. Your services will be \nconfirmed after successful completion of three months and subject to your performance and timely evaluation of your \nwork process. The period of probation can be extended at the discretion of the Management, and you will continue \nto be on probation till an order of confirmation has been issued in writing. \n \nSome additional points: \nò \nSoftStandard Solutions LLP., hold rights to all the intellectual property developed during your employment. \nò \nAll work and discussions are confidential and are not to be discussed or published outside the company, except with \nan agreement by the Director \nò \nExternal work with another party has to be agreed with the Director in writing in advance. Compliance with SoftStandard \nSolutions LLP., non-compete policy in employment contract. \nTermination of Employment:  \na. Your employment/ services will be governed by CompanyÆs rules and regulations applicable from time to time. If \nthe Company is not satisfied with your performance on any account, the Company reserves the right to terminate your \nemployment with a notice of 15 days or by paying proportionate salary in lieu of any short notice only if you are a \nconfirmed Permanent employee of the organization. This in no way limits the CompanyÆs right to terminate your \nemployment without notice in the event of serious misconduct which include, committing a criminal offence, theft, \nfraud, embezzlement, intoxication, violence, sexual harassment, damage to the CompanyÆs reputation etc. \n  \n b. The Company reserves the right to terminate your services without giving any reasons during probation, not giving \nany kind of compensation or Notice as mentioned in point "a".'
Block 2 (x=18.0, y=793.9 to 804.9): ''
Block 0 (x=33.0, y=812.7 to 824.5): 'SoftStandard Solutions LLP I Plot no 201 & 202, Kavuri Hills Rd, Guttala_Begumpet, Kavuri Hills, Hyderabad, 5500033.'

================ PAGE 2 ================
Block 1 (x=18.0, y=8.3 to 19.4): ''
